

### **Contact**

551-998-7611

■ homesbygabby@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielaespinal

www.homesbygabbie.com

## Skills

Yardi
Sales
Marketing
Real Estate
MS Outlook
MS Word
MS Excel

## Certifications

### Indeed

Computer Skills: PC Expert

Real Estate Proficient

Customer Focus & Orientation

Highly Proficient

#### LinkedIn

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word Microsoft Outlook

# About me



Assistant Property Management with 5+ years of experience seeking new opportunities where my customer service background and education can be utilized to the fullest, providing customers with the highest quality of service and investors with a high rate of return on their investment. Hospitality Management Associate. Real Estate License in process. Personable, organized and task-oriented.

# **Experience**



#### 1170 Apartment Corp

Assistant Property Manager New Jersey, United States

O Jan 2016 - Present

(4 years, 6 months)

- \*Help manage 26 Buildings for a total of 1170 units in a 35 acres land \*Advertise units and negotiate lease terms
- \*Perform tenant screenings
- \*Experience with Yardi, Outlook, Excel and Microsoft Word
- \*Act as liaison between tenants and property owners
- \*Responsible for implementing lease renewal
- \*Collect rent on a monthly basis and handle late payments in a timely manner
- \*Maintain property by addressing tenant complaints, completing repairs, and occupancy
- \*Coordinate maintenance schedule with Maintenance Coordinator
- \*Create, mentor and manage a cohesive property maintenance team

### Smart Realty

O Jan 2019-Present (1 years, 6 months)

Property Sales Consultant / Leasing Specialist

New Jersey, United States

- \*Generating leads and turning them into opportunities for sales and rentals
- \*Contacting potential customers via telephone & email
- \*Arranging meetings with prospects in order to tour property
- \*Front office customer service
- \*Preparing lease documentation, property inspections, completing move-in and out paperwork and procedures

## **Education**



#### Real Estate

O Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Kovats Real Estate School

### Associate's Degree

O Dec 2010-Jan 2014

Hospitality Administration / Management

Bergen Community College

- \*Overseeing personnel, ensuring that the facilities are properly maintained, taking steps to ensure customer satisfaction and overseeing the upkeep of administrative and financial records.
- \*Accounting
- \*Economics
- \*Marketing, and human resource management.
- \*Safety and health prevention norms.